bestezines.com 2002-12-10

# BestEzines Privacy Statement

BestEzines.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Best-Ezines.com.

We respect your privacy! Any and all information collected at this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, loaned, or otherwise disclosed. Any information you give to Best-Ezines.com will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. A more detailed explanation about how we safeguard your personal information is described below. If you have any questions, please don't hesitate to let us know.

This site contains links to other sites. BestEzines.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.

**1.** You can send email to [support@bestezines.com](mailto:support@bestezines.com)  
**2.** You can visit the following URL: http://BestEzines.com/

Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.

**1.** email  [support@bestezines.com](mailto:support@bestezines.com)  
**2.** visit http://BestEzines.com/

Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: 

Christopher M. Knight  
BestEzines.com  
1592 Union Street, Suite 185  
San Francisco, CA 94123  

* * *
